Presenter: OK, Team B, now you have thirty seconds to ask Mike questions.
But remember Mike can only answer Yes or No.
Alice: Hello, Mike. Do you wear a uniform or special clothes?
Mike: Yes, I do. Not a uniform, but special clothes.
George: Do you have special qualifications?
Mike: Yes, I do.
Charlie: Do you work in a team?
Mike: No. But sometimes other people help me.
Presenter: Remember Mike, you can only answer yes or no.
Mike: Oh yes. Sorry.
Alice: Do you work inside?
Mike: Yes, I do.
George: Do you work at the weekend?
Mike: No, I don’t.
Charlie: Do you like your job?
Mike: Yes, I love it. But people don’t always like me!
Presenter: Thank you, Mike. So, Team B, is Mike a hairdresser, a chef, or a dentist?
You have one minute.